UX DESIGNER

Tierre Middleton

PROFILE

UX/UI designer with over 5 years experience in customer service. Experienced in creating solutions for customers in order to maintain high satisfaction rates as evidenced by exceeding thousands of customer expectations. Due to my passion of assisting others and creating inventive solutions, UX/UI is my perfect match.

EXPERIENCE

CREW MEMBER, MCDONALD'S; HOOVER, AL 2014-2015

- Greet customers
- Cashier
- Maintain lobby cleanliness

MERCHANDISE ASSOCIATE, TJ MAXX; PASO ROBLES, CA 2016-2018

- Greet customers
- Answer phone calls
- Cashier
- Cash office
- Organize items to optimize sales

FRONT DESK RECEPTIONIST, KENNEDY CLUB FITNESS; PASO ROBLES 2017-2018

- Answer over 500 phone calls
- Create membership passes
- Clean all areas of the facility
- Responsible for over \$5000 revenue transactions

HOUSEKEEPER, TREANA WINERY 2017-2018

Maintain cleanliness of offices and all other areas of the facility

DENTAL ASSISTANT, K YOUNG HEE SUSAN LEE, DDS; BARSTOW, CA 2019-2020

- Take x-rays
- Clean teeth
- Enter treatment information
- Explain treatment to patients
- Four hand dentistry
- Take impressions and pour cast model

Clean instruments

DENTAL ASSISTANT, K YOUNG HEE SUSAN LEE, DDS; BARSTOW, CA 2019-2020

- Take x-rays
- Clean teeth
- Enter treatment into Dentrix and Open Dental
- Explain treatment to patients
- Enhanced time management by scheduling appointments
- Answer calls
- Four hand dentistry
- Selected to train new employees
- · iTero scanning
- Assist with Invisalign
- Social media management
- Create work manual for new employees

EDUCATION

Bessemer City High School – Diploma, 2015

Cuesta College - 2015-2016

USCI – Dental Assistant, 2017-2019

Careerfoundry – UX Design, Frontend Development, 2022-2023

SKILLS

- Attentive listener
- Team player
- Detail oriented
- Ability to multitask
- Quick learner
- Punctual

TOOLS

- Figma
- Balsamiq
- Marvel
- HTML
- Google sheets
- Excel
- PowerPoint